Rong A-52
As long as you help me get this done,
you will all be handsomely rewarded.
Whoever provides the most useful material
gets the biggest reward.
If
you're afraid of being exposed
and want to leave the He family,
I promise
you can all come work for the Liang Group,
and your salary will be doubled.
But...
If anyone wants to snitch,
don't forget,
I have
your families' information.
Alright,
let's go.
Hurry up, He Shi.
Take your time, He Shi.
Strange.
Why do I feel like someone is watching me?
What,
you like being watched?
Wait a minute.
Come on, baby.
Recently,
someone anonymously tipped off our agency
about the secret affair
between Mrs. He of the He Group
and the eldest son,
He Shi.
Miss Liang is
quite resourceful.
If I tried to bribe the nanny,
it might not have worked,
because in the He family,
they would trust Mrs. He more.
But with the power of the Liang Group,
this matter
became much easier.
You've got some nerve.
I just got back from the hospital,
and you dare to cause such a scandal.
Master, I was wrong.
Where is that bastard He Shi?
Tell him to get out here.
I'll deal with him
today too.
What happened?
He Shi hasn't been back all night.
Haven't you all seen the news?
She has completely disgraced
our He family.
Speak.
When did this start?
Mrs. He has fainted.
Let me see.
Li Zhangxin,
you venomous woman!
Mrs. He, your skill at faking a faint
is truly impressive.
Bring me the whip.
Coming, Dad.
Here you go, Dad.
You...
Sir, I was wrong.
Please spare me, Sir!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Sir!
-I'll beat you to death!
-Sir!
I've painstakingly stayed
by your side for over a decade.
Don't you remember
our past affection at all?
Shut up!
In ancient times,
you would have been drowned
in a pig basket.
From today on,
you are no longer Mrs. He
of the He family.
Get out of here!
I don't want to leave!
Sir,
please calm down!
I'm not leaving!
Fine,
just you wait!
Mr. He,
you bastard!
Are you satisfied now?
I know the butler is dead.
Where is he?
I won't tell you.
You've been beaten for a whole day,
and he hasn't shown up.
Do you think
he will still come to save you?
Get
lost!
I apologize.
My personal affairs
have taken up public resources.
I'd like to say
sorry to everyone here.
Actually, this relationship
wasn't my intention.
It was all because Zhang Xin
seduced me into sleeping with her
when I was young and naive.
I really didn't expect things
to turn out like this.
Please wait, Mr. He.
The stepmother trope becomes reality.
Do you have some sort of Oedipus complex?
What is Mr. He Senior's stance
on you fighting your own father
for a woman?
Yeah,
what is his stance?
Please say a few words. Tell us.
Mr. He,
It's all because Zhang Xin
seduced me into sleeping with her.
He Shi!
You bastard.
See how he saves his own skin?
Even now,
you're still taking his side.
Do you think I'm stupid?
If I tell you where the butler is,
not only will He Shi go to jail,
but I'll be implicated too.
Fine.
Then you can just tear each other apart.
Damn He Shi.
How much for this watch?
In all of Rongcheng,
only the eldest son
of the He family has this watch.
Could you be
his new lover?
Cut the crap. How much?
I can't take it.
Why?
This watch is fake.
It's fake.
He Shi,
you bastard!
I shouldn't have trusted Zhang Xin.
Our He family
is ruined by her.
Dad,
Zhang Xin is behind all this.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Mei,
I've failed you and your mother.
I promise you,
from now on,
I won't see any other women.
Zhang Xin
doesn't deserve to be
on our He family tree.
Thank you, Dad.
You don't still resent me, do you?
I've never blamed you.
Dad!
Are you okay?
Dad, are you okay? Dad!
Dad!
Somebody help!
Good things happen to good people.
Dad will be fine.
Miss, Second Young Master,
the recent turmoil might have
taken a toll on the Master.
Given his current condition,
he needs a bone marrow transplant
immediately.
Your bone marrow
is a perfect match for his.
This is the surgery consent form.
Please take a look.
You will be responsible
for any complications
during the surgery.
Don't you want to read it carefully first?
It's a major surgery, after all.
I'll do anything
as long as it can save Dad.